[theme music playing]
I hate you!
I did everything to make you mine!
[Nimfa] I let her control me!
-[Diego] Nimfa!
-I became a bad person!
[Diego] What did you say?
[Diego] Ivy, I don't know how
Nimfa could do this to me, either.
That's why we shouldn't allow them to win.
You need to mislead Emilia.
She can't discover your true identity.
We're going to hunt Lily Cruz.
[woman] Haven't you heard?
Emilia's nabbing all the women
who are the same age as Lily Cruz.
[Ivy] What will you do to them?
Where are you taking them?
[Emilia] I won't do anything
today that you won't like.
[Camia] You're going to kidnap the women
here to find Lily Cruz.
Yes, Emilia. I know all about
your dirty games.
Boys, now!
[Camia] Fine, Emilia.
Because I don't want
these people to get hurt,
I'll come with you.
[Emilia] Is Lily alive?! Where is she?!
[Camia] Yes, Lily is alive!
[Emilia] Will she resurface?
Is she going to press charges?
Lily will not resurface.
I promise you that.
[Camia] The Ardientes already know
that Lily is still alive.
I think I need to talk to my daughter.
[Nimfa] I'm sure about this,
Ma'am Emilia. Lily's coming.
[Emilia] Take a video, and send
it to me immediately.
If you pull that off, you're free to go.
Good job.
[Nimfa cries]
[Camia] Let go of me!
How dare you! You liar!
How could you do this?
What were you thinking?
Emilia promised to give me a better life.
I was blinded by it…
Emilia promised me
you'd be mine after all this.
Well, she lied to you!
I did all this hoping
I could make you love me, Diego!
[Nimfa] But you only have eyes for Ivy…
for Lily.
[Nimfa] You're being nice to me
so I won't push through with my plan.
I'm still telling Emilia about
the information I discovered!
Get out of my way!
Nimfa!
[all] ♪ Happy birthday, happy birthday ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Cheers! Thank you, thank you!
[clapping and cheering]
[Carlito] Have your seats, everybody.
Tonight, let us celebrate.
And so, let us forget about politics.
All right? Just for tonight. [chuckles]
And, help yourselves
to some drinks and some food.
Let's have fun.
All right. Enjoy the night.
[clapping]
[cha-cha music playing]
[Emilia] Come on.
Let's go up to the senator.
I'm sure he still remembers me
from our Paris trip.
I was still a governor then.
Hold on. Just stay there. You stay.
You're too excited. Relax.
But, we shouldn't waste this opportunity
to win his endorsement!
Emilia! Cállate!
Act like an Ardiente.
[Julio] We don't approach people…
people approach us.
[cha-cha music continues playing]
[Nimfa panting]
Out of my way! Let me go! Out of my way!
-Nimfa!
-I said out of my way!
-Don't let her go!
-Let go of me!
[crying]
Just let me go! I said let me go!
[Nimfa crying]
[Carlito] Thank you for coming
to my birthday.
[guest] Thank you.
Senator!
[Carlito] Ah.
[cha-cha music playing]
Governor Emilia.
Happy birthday, Senator.
What a lovely party.
Thank you.
How can I forget your birthday?
And you, Senator.
I made sure to include
your thrust on national security
and tourism in my platform.
Of course. How could I forget,
Governor Emilia?
You copied Victorino's platform too.
Wasn't he your opponent
in the last election?
[tense music playing]
[Carlito] We didn't expect him to win
because your family controls
all of Poblacion Ardiente.
Ah, Miss Aguas.
Senator O!
[Carlito] I thought we'd meet sooner.
[Carlito] Engaged?
Yes.
Who's the lucky guy? [chuckles]
Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo, Senator.
Well, I should say this.
Remember when we were
preparing the details
for the low-cost housing project?
-Yes, of course.
-[Carlito] I think…
I should've courted you back then.
[Ivy and Carlito chuckle]
If only, Senator.
But I'm sure my mother
wouldn't have allowed it.
[Carlito laughs]
Ouch, that hurt. Point well taken.
[tense music playing]
[crying]
[Emilia] I will lift you out of poverty.
I'll make you a very rich woman.
[Claire] I can guarantee you,
you'll be able to provide
for your father after this.
[Nimfa] You won't just give me the house,
the car, and the money.
Diego.
I want Diego to be mine after all this.
And you'll help me make that happen.
[Diego] Nimfa, wait.
Can we not ruin what we have?
[muffled shriek]
[Diego] Why did you do that?!
Haven't you realized
that they're just using you?
You know Emilia and her family
are murderers and liars!
I did all this hoping
I could make you love me, Diego!
I may have done the wrong thing.
But, there's no turning back now.
[Carlito chuckles] It's an honor
to have you here.
-[Julio] Thank you.
-I'm really flattered, Senator.
[Emilia] You didn't forget about us.
[Carlito] Of course.
Your family is unforgettable.
Especially to the victims
of the human rights violations
you committed.
Excuse me?
[Carlito] Actually,
we have an international publication
present to do an in-depth investigation
on the killings your family
is implicated in.
[chuckles]
This is unbelievable, Senator.
[Julio] Anyway…
It's your birthday.
Enjoy your celebration.
[Julio] But right now,
I suggest you shut up.
I know it's your birthday, but I
just might make it your last.
[Ivy] Congressman. Congressman!
Senator.
How about we…
set our pride and our tempers aside…
and make this a productive discussion--
[Arnaldo] Ivy.
-[whispers] Don't.
-Hon, it's okay.
Senator, the truth is we came
to ask for your endorsement
so that Arnaldo could join
your party, if you'll allow it.
Well, go on. You know…
[Carlito] Um. I might've said
some harsh words earlier,
but I could learn
to sing a different tune.
[Carlito] If necessary.
[Arnaldo] Excuse me.
-[Julio] Oh, well.
-Excuse me.
[Julio] Well, well.
I guess that's our cue
to end this little charade.
[Julio clears throat]
Senator Olivares, thank you very much
for your warm and candid words.
One day, Senator. One day.
I hope before that day comes…
your family will be held accountable…
for all the violations you've committed.
And,
that your province gets back all the money
you stole from them.
Ha.
[Julio] Tell it to the marines, Carlito.
Then again, what makes you
better than us, huh?
Everyone knows that you're the leader…
of the largest drug cartel in the country.
We all have our own territories.
And, please.
Don't give me that
saintly stance and look of yours
just because you've seen differently.
Let's go.
[tense music playing]
[Ivy] Hon. Arnaldo.
I said wait, hon! What's
going on? What's wrong?
What's your relationship with Olivares?
[tense music playing]
Relationship?
Hon, you heard us earlier.
I was just part of his company's
low-cost housing project.
That's it.
Arnaldo, are you jealous again?
-We have to go.
-No!
Not yet. What about your endorsement?
I don't care about the endorsement!
I'll form my own party for all I care,
just stop acting like a cheap whore--
How dare you say that to me?
You dare say that to me
when I'm doing everything I can
to get that endorsement?
WE NEED TO TALK…
[tense music continues playing]
Arnaldo, it's starting to bruise--
Shut it. Leave me alone.
Come on, son…
You have every reason to be angry at Ivy.
But she told me she's known
the senator for a long time.
That's why she scored us
invites to this party.
[tense music swells]
Arnaldo, don't get me wrong…
But does your fiancée really love you?
Or worse, maybe she brought
you here to set you up.
Shut up!
Maybe she wants the people
to see you fail!
Shut up!
That's not true!
Okay, go ahead. Follow her!
That way, you'll see that
she doesn't really love you.
Go!
Crazy!
[suspenseful music playing]
Nimfa?
[gasps]
Nimfa, what did you do?
We need to go to the hospital.
Guards! Guards!
Guard!
What is it, ma'am?
Get the car.
We need to go to the hospital!
We need to bring Nimfa! Hurry!
Yes, ma'am!
[ominous music playing]
I'll make Emilia pay.
But I need to get out of here first.
[sighs deeply]
Nimfa, think. Use your brain cells.
[tense music playing]
[shatters]
Ah!
[tense music playing]
[tense music swelling]
Nimfa… Nimfa, what did you do?
[whimpers]
I can't take it anymore.
Nimfa, we're here to take care of you.
I can't do it anymore.
We'll take care of you. Come on.
Let's go to the hospital. Come on. Get up!
-[Nimfa] Ma'am Camia…
-[Camia screams]
[Nimfa panting]
Pick up, Emilia. Pick up, Emilia.
[phone rings]
Pick up!
[Julio] Emilia.
Come with me. We're going somewhere.
But I'm not going home yet.
I'm going somewhere.
We aren't going home.
I need to show you something.
[Julio] Now, follow me.
Let's go.
[tense music swells]
[groans] Nimfa? Nimfa!
-Pick up!
-[phone dialing]
[phone ringing]
Hello, Nimfa?
Hello, Ma'am Emilia!
Ma'am Emilia. I know the truth!
Ivy Aguas and Lily--
-No!
-[Nimfa squeals]
What? I can't hear you.
-Give me that!
-No, give it back!
Hello? I'll call you back, okay?
[Claire] What happened?
Give me that!
How dare you make a fool out of me?!
After everything I did for you!
Give me that!
I won't let you go to Emilia!
You can't leave this place!
-[Camia grunts]
-Give me that!
I won't let you tell
the truth to Emilia! [screams]
-Guard!
-Emilia is my only hope…
to have a better life!
Ouch! Guard! Guard!
[Camia screams]
[suspenseful music playing]
Nimfa! Nimfa!
Nimfa! Nimfa! Nimfa!
[suspenseful music continues playing]
Nimfa! Nimfa!
[Camia] After her! Hurry!
Nimfa!
[door opens]
[Julio] Yes!
We might need Olivares' help,
but we are not beggars, Emilia.
I just want to show you
how much power and wealth
our family possesses.
Take a look.
With that kind of firepower and money…
we can turn the most innocent soul…
into a hungry, greedy dog
who will do anything for us.
Things that make the world go round.
Guns and money.
And we have them both.
[car door closes]
-Ivy.
-Diego.
[suspenseful music playing]
Ivy, it's Nimfa.
She's the one who told Emilia
that Lily is still alive.
[suspenseful music swells]
[whispers] Arnaldo.
-Arnaldo's here.
-What?!
Hon?
[suspenseful music playing]
Arnaldo.
-Hon.
-We're not doing anything wrong.
Hon, I can explain.
Thank you.
-[Diego grunts]
-[Ivy] Arnaldo!
Arnaldo, enough!
[Ivy] Stop it. We should go home.
Arnaldo. I'll tell you why I'm here, hon.
Let's go, hon. Let's go.
Let's go.
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[crickets chirping]
[sighs]
How long have you been meeting with Diego?
[tense music playing]
Answer me.
For a while now.
[tense music playing]
So, what were you two doing there?
You were there, weren't you? You saw us.
What you saw was the only thing
we were doing.
We were simply talking.
[scoffs] You were just talking.
Yeah, right. Okay.
What were you talking about, then?
How the two of you
will stab me behind my back?
Am I right?
Tell me.
Hello, Aunt Camia.
I already warned Ivy about Nimfa.
I'm on my way there.
[Camia] Diego, don't.
Nimfa got away.
I'm sure she'll go to Emilia
and tell her who Ivy really is.
Diego, you have to stop her.
I will, Aunt Camia.
[tense music playing]
[engine revving up]
This again, huh?
Earlier at the party,
you told me I was acting
like a cheap whore.
Now, you're telling me
I'm cheating on you.
[tense music playing]
Arnaldo, please.
As the woman you promised to
marry and love wholeheartedly…
and as your fiancée…
I assure you…
of my loyalty.
I'm all yours, Arnaldo--
Bullshit!
[breathing heavily]
[tense music swells]
Arnaldo, what's with you?
Do we always have to be like this?
Do you always have to be jealous?
Do we always have to fight
because of your jealousy?
Earlier, you were jealous of
Senator Olivares.
This time, you're jealous of Diego.
Diego is just a friend.
We aren't what you think we are!
Like I said earlier, he's just a friend.
And you…
I'm all yours, Arnaldo.
I'm all yours.
All yours. Please believe me.
I will be yours forever.
[tense music playing]
[Ivy whimpers]
But it's like you don't believe me…
you don't trust me anymore.
Now, you're labeling me as a traitor.
If you don't believe me,
if you think I'm betraying you…
I guess, Arnaldo… Let's just stop this.
We should call off our wedding.
You just broke my heart, Mr. Mayor.
[tense music swells]
Seven, six, five…
Don't disappoint me, Arnaldo.
Four, three, two, and…
[Arnaldo] Ivy!
[Arnaldo sobbing] Ivy!
Ivy, please…
[bawling] Don't leave me! Don't leave me!
Don't leave me! Please. Don't leave me.
I won't let you.
You can't leave me. You can't…
Please don't go!
[sobbing] Please!
No… No, Arnaldo!
-[Arnaldo sniffles]
-You hurt me!
[cries]
I'm sorry. My decision is final.
-[Arnaldo] No. No.
-[Ivy] No!
-I've made up my mind.
-Please, no!
How you're acting…
made me think twice
about my decision to marry you.
I'm really reconsidering everything now.
No!
You can't leave me!
Don't leave me! Don't leave me!
Don't leave me!
-I'm sorry.
-Arnaldo. Arnaldo.
No… I'm sorry! Sorry! I'm sorry!
[bawling] Sorry! Please, Ivy.
No, Arnaldo!
We should spend some time apart.
[exhales]
Arnaldo…
-No, no, no, no!
-Arnaldo…
-You can't leave me! [sobs]
-Arnaldo, I have to go!
We should spend some time apart.
[Arnaldo sniffles]
Ivy!
[tense music playing]
Ivy…
[phone rings]
Hello?
Ma'am E!
[suspenseful sting]
This is Emilia Ardiente, right?!
Camia?!
[Camia] Don't hang up.
I already know that Nimfa's your spy.
Where is she? What did you do to her?!
You're asking me?
Shouldn't I be asking you that?
Just tell me where she is!
[suspenseful music playing]
[tense music swells]
[Emilia] Why can't you
accept the fact that
Ivy's just playing you?
Who knows? She's with Diego.
[Arnaldo] You're toying with me!
[Ivy] Of course not! No!
[Arnaldo] What's going on between you two?
[Ivy] Diego and I still see each other.
But I told him to stay away.
Because I know I'm sure
of my feelings for you.
Arnaldo, I'm not toying with you.
I love you. I love you, Arnaldo.
[Emilia] You have every
reason to be angry at Ivy.
Does your fiancée really love you?
Or worse, maybe she brought
you here to set you up.
[Arnaldo] Shut up!
[Emilia] Maybe she wants
the people to see you fail!
[Arnaldo] Shut up!
[Emilia] Go ahead… Follow her!
That way, you'll see that
she doesn't really love you.
[Ivy] Arnaldo! Arnaldo, enough!
Arnaldo. I'm all yours.
If you don't believe me,
if you think I'm betraying you,
I guess, Arnaldo… Let's just stop this.
[Ivy] We should call off our wedding.
You just broke my heart, Mr. Mayor.
[tense music swells]
This is the only way to get you
out of our lives, Diego.
[suspenseful music playing]
Ma'am Emilia?
Ma'am?
Where is she?
Nimfa, where are you?
Ma'am, you have a visitor.
-Ma'am Camia.
-Miss Loring.
Ma'am, I'm sorry for coming unannounced.
I tried calling you.
But I couldn't get a hold of you.
-[Camia] Why--
-Good evening, Ma'am Camia.
I traveled all the way from Bacolod.
I just have a nagging feeling
something's not right.
I'm worried about my daughter, Nimfa.
[suspenseful music swells]
[Nimfa] Ma'am Emilia.
Ma'am?
[Nimfa] Ma'am Emilia?
Mayor Arnaldo!
What are you doing here?
Where is Ma'am Emilia?
I need to tell her something.
You're from the co-op?
So, you're Mom's spy.
Where is she?
I need to tell her something
about Miss Ivy.
Ivy?
What about her?
You shouldn't trust her.
I know you love her, Mayor.
But she's just using you.
That's not true. You're lying.
Mayor, she's the one feeding
information to Diego's camp!
-That's not true!
-She's Diego's spy…
-within the Ardiente family!
She's just using you.
That's not true!
[Emilia] Ivy's just playing you.
Actually, playing us.
Does your fiancée really love you?
[Nimfa] She's just using you.
That's not--
Mayor, you need to know that Ivy is--
-That's not true!
-[gunshot]
[gunshot in distance]
[Ivy] Damn you, Arnaldo.
I'm not done with you yet.
-[Arnaldo screaming]
-[gunshots]
[suspenseful music swells]
Go back. Go back there.
Mayor!
Clean that up.
[tense music playing]
[Ivy] Arnaldo?
Arnaldo?
[suspenseful music playing]
Arnaldo!
[suspenseful music continues playing]
I heard gunshots. I thought--
I thought you left me for good.
But you came back for me.
Were you worried about me?
Ivy.
Take back your ring.
Please take back your ring.
And let's just forget…
-about everything that happened.
-No, Arnaldo.
No.
Not until you change.
We'll just keep doing this.
[Arnaldo] You can't refuse
me anymore. All right?
-You will take this ring…
-Arnaldo.
And you will marry me
whether you like it--
Arnaldo!
Ahh!
[motorcycle approaching]
Sir.
Is Nimfa there?
The one from the co-op?
She's this tall and slender.
We haven't had any visitors, sir.
Stop it!
Don't you see it, hmm?
See, I'm the only one
who believes in your stories.
Or should I say, lies?
I keep looking the other way
because I'm blinded by my love for you.
You've constantly made a fool out of me.
But I just accept it. Because I love you.
I love you so much.
Why? What did you find out?
Maybe she's inside.
No one came, sir.
Thank you.
Okay.
[engine revving]
From now on, everything will change.
You will love me. You will marry me.
And you won't have any other choice.
What did you learn?
Okay.
You really wanna know?
Then let's start with…
how you're the one supporting
and helping finance
the case Camia filed
against the Ardientes.
And, oh!
You also help in Diego's campaign.
What a freaking surprise.
Ivy Aguas.
You're a traitor to the Ardientes.
And, most importantly,
you betrayed the man
you said you were in love with.
[tense music continues playing]
That's not true.
Isn't it?
Yes.
Well, how can you deny it?
That's what Mom's spy said earlier.
How do I know?
Because right at this very spot,
Nimfa dropped dead.
That's right.
I killed her.
After she told me everything you'd done.
You killed Nimfa?
Well…
My mind is telling me
to believe her, but my heart…
This… this thing…
This thing refuses
to take orders from anyone.
That's why I killed her.
[crickets chirping]
Miss Loring, Mister Fernan…
-Diego's here.
-Nanny.
Mister Fernan.
[Loring] Diego!
Did you find Nimfa?
Is she with the Ardientes?
[Fernan] Why…
What's she doing with Emilia?
She works here, right?
Is there something you're not telling me?
Did something happen to my daughter?
[Loring] Diego, what's happening?
Please tell us.
[tense music playing]
Nimfa is my friend.
So, I couldn't believe
what happened, either.
[Loring] What?
Nimfa is Emilia's spy.
She was bribed with
money and other things.
Emilia told her to spy on our
party and sabotage my campaign.
No. My daughter wouldn't do that!
[Fernan] Where's Nimfa? Nimfa!
[Diego] Mister Fernan.
-[Fernan] Nimfa!
-Mister Fernan.
Your daughter was here a while ago,
but she went to Emilia.
She hasn't come back yet.
[tense music playing]
[Fernan] Loring.
-My daughter!
-[Loring] Fernan.
Mister Fernan, we'll get
to the bottom of this.
Be strong.
So, here's what's going to happen.
[huffs]
We'll push through with the wedding.
Because your whole act
will be for nothing…
if we don't have our royal wedding.
[tense music playing]
Wait, wait…
You're upset again!
I don't like it when you're upset, please.
Please. Please. We're getting married.
I love you so much. I love you so much.
[sniffles]
I love you so much, please.
Please. I love you!
[bawling]
I love you. Ivy, I love you.
Ivy! I love you so much!
Please, don't let me down.
I killed for you.
I killed for you. What more do you want?
I killed for you!
That's how much I love you, Ivy.
Anything for you!
I love you so much, please!
Please, don't let me down! Please!
Please!
We will only get married…
if you believe me…
when I say I'm not
a traitor to your family.
I need my name cleared
because I'm not a traitor to your family.
You need to believe me, Arnaldo,
not that farmhand.
If you believe me, we'll get married.
I-- I believe you.
I-- Ivy, I believe you!
I believe you. I believe you.
I believe everything that you say.
Ivy, that's it. I believe you.
I believe you.
That's all I need.
I need you to trust me.
That's all, Arnaldo.
I'm not a traitor.
Do you believe me?
I do.
I believe you.
I love you so much.
And I'll marry you again.
We're going through with the wedding.
[sniffles]
We're going through
with the wedding, okay?
-Yes.
-We're getting married, right?
Yes.
[tense music playing]
But wait, Arnaldo…
I need time to process all this.
You need to take some time too.
I'm worried about you.
You're not a murderer.
How are you going to cover up
what you did to Nimfa?
[stammering]
That's nothing. You don't need
to worry about that.
I've taken care of it.
I know exactly who should take the fall,
so don't worry. Don't worry!
Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine! I'll be fine.
[tense music swells]
Hon?
[Diego] Arnaldo.
-Hon.
-We're not doing anything wrong.
-[Diego grunts]
-[Ivy] Arnaldo! Arnaldo, enough!
Ah…
An angel just flew over us!
[Julio chuckles]
Or at least,
I think that's what people say
when silence befalls
a gathering like this.
But, then again, with this family…
I don't think that's applicable.
It's more like…
a demon passed by!
[chuckles]
Because I can only think
of wicked things and thoughts…
that are running within each
and every mind at this table.
Well, Emilia…
Would you care to share
your evil thoughts?
No, Papa.
[Julio] How about you, Arnaldo?
What ungodly secret is running
through your head right now?
Nothing, Grandpa. That secret
shall reveal itself very soon.
But, is everything okay between
you and your future wife?
[tense music swells]
Excuse me, I'll just use the restroom.
[Julio sighs]
I didn't know I had that effect.
Well, I'm done. Excuse me.
Me too.
I am still head of this family!
The least you can do…
is tell me what the hell is going on.
Okay, Papa…
I'm worried because my spy
hasn't checked in with me yet.
I'm afraid she might have turned on me.
Arnaldo.
Did you have anything to do with this?
Well, I guess there's no point
in keeping it a secret.
Nimfa is dead, and I killed her.
Oh, my--
[tense music playing]
[lock clicking]
[phone rings]
Hello, Ivy?
Diego…
Diego-- Diego, something
happened to Nimfa.
What--
Ivy-- Ivy, what happened to her?
Diego, she's…
She's dead.
Arnaldo killed her.
[tense music swells]
-[Fernan] Nimfa! Nimfa!
-[Loring screams]
-[Diego] Mr. Fernan!
-[Fernan] Nimfa!
Why did they kill my daughter?
[Diego] Their day will come.
[man] This is solid evidence, Mr. Torillo.
We'll raid this armory
as soon as possible.
[goon] Congressman, someone's coming.
-[gunshots]
-They're armed.
Special Forces from Manila.
[police officer] Mr. Torillo, we
have a warrant for your arrest
for the murder of Nimfa Naig.
What did you do to Diego?
[Arnaldo] It was a frame-up.
And it was so easy.
-[grunting]
-[Emilia] Raul! Stop it!
[camera shutter clicking]
[theme music playing]